Johnathan Raymond

Atlanta, Georgia 678-428-5263 johnathan.raymond07@gmail.com

SUMMARY

UX Design has been my passion for 2 years. My natural curiosity for demystifying the human frustration with technology has led to over a dozen clients satisfied. With skills such as lo-to-high fidelity wireframing, usability testing, and effective collaboration with developers and project managers, has led to multiple victories punctually met and executed simply, functionally, and beautifully.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Designer

Mobile App Hero Aug 2017-present

- Improved interface of app/web design
- Streamlined usability for web/mobile applications
- Generated and analyzed competitive research
- Implemented modern design techniques to enhance interactivity
- Mastered Low/high fidelity wireframing for planning structure
- Collaborated with clients and developers for seamless functionality
- Updated quality assurance for application after build process

Freelance UX/UI Designer

Self-employed Jun 2016 - present

- Produced designs for iOS/Android/web applications
- · Created lo-to-hi fidelity wireframes assisted with logic flows
- · Provided direction for UI design
- Discovered infographics reports for clients

Director of Photography/Videography

The Extra Yard LLC Aug 2016 - Aug 2017

- · Established visuals
- Worked closely with product designers and art directors
- · Managed prep and take-down of equipment

Freelance Photographer/Videographer

Self Employed Jan 2015 - present

- Session consultation with clients
- Scheduled photo/video shoots
- Photo-editing/video-editing
- Directed/produced shoot based of client needs and wants

SKILLS

Design



Research



Coding



- User-centric design
- · Low/high fidelity prototyping
- Personas
- Face to face interviewing
- Usability-testing
- Close collaborative work with developers, PMs'
- Information architecture
- · Brainstorm coordination
- MS certified & Apple certified
- Adobe CC, Sketch, Invision
- HTML5/CSS3

EDUCATION

Faulkner State Community College

- Computer Science, 2013

CERTIFICATE

Career Foundry

Human Centered Design, 2017

Project Manager

Paxadise Arts Jul 2015 - Sep 2017

- Managed artist of Paxadise arts
- Supervised overall progress of project and artist' venues
- Authorized next project venture
- Economized/monitored finances with arbitrage

Freight Associate

Home Depot March 2016 - February 2017

- Unpacked, examined and routed incoming trucks
- · moved material from the receiving area throughout the store
- performed critical functions for maintaining proper hands-on and pricing for customers
- · rejected damaged items and recorded shortages,
- · Received and processed all defective parts returned for replacement or credit

Lifestyle Specialist

Best Buy August 2014 - February 2017

- Brought in \$30,000 of sales revenue each month
- Provided knowledgeable and impartial advice to each customer
- Up-to-date with older, modern, and advanced consumer and business technology